<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="error_title">An error has occurred</string>

  <string name="err_connection_error">No connection found. Please check your network configuration and retry.</string>
  <string name="err_server_error">The server is unavailable.</string>
  <string name="err_not_logged">Invalid user or password.</string>
  <string name="err_version_error">You are using a different version from the server. The fruit name in both version must match. Please make updates accordingly.</string>

  <string name="err_cashreg_not_found">Cash register not found. Please check the machine name in configuration to match a registered one</string>
  <string name="err_unknown_location">Invalid stock location. Please check your configuration.</string>

  <string name="err_load_error">Unable to restore all data. Please update data before starting.</string>
  <string name="err_save_session">Unable to save session. You may lose tickets that were not paid already.</string>
  <string name="err_save_catalog">Unable to save catalog. Quitting the application may leave no products available.</string>
  <string name="err_save_compositions">Unable to save compositions. Quitting the application may leave compositions unaffected.</string>
  <string name="err_save_tariff_areas">Unable to save tariff areas. Quitting the application may leave no area available.</string>
  <string name="err_save_payment_modes">Unable to save payment modes. Quitting the application may leave no way to pay tickets.</string>
  <string name="err_save_users">Unable to save users. Quitting the application may prevent you to log in.</string>
  <string name="err_save_customers">Unable to save customers. Quitting the application may leave no customers available.</string>
  <string name="err_save_cash_register">Unable to save cash register. Opening a new cash may result in strange behaviour</string>
  <string name="err_save_cash">Unable to save cash state. Open/close date may be lost when leaving the application.</string>
  <string name="err_no_cash">No cash found. Updating data may solve the problem</string>
  <string name="err_save_receipts">Unable to save receipts. You may lose them if you quit the application without sending the data to the server.</string>
  <string name="err_save_places">Unable to save places. You may lose them if you quit the application.</string>
  <string name="err_save_stocks">Unable to save stocks. You may not be able to check your stock you quit the application.</string>
  <string name="err_save_resource">Unable to save resource. Some features may be missing.</string>
  <string name="err_load_archive">Unable to load a previous cash session.</string>

  <string name="err_sync">The synchronization failed partially or totally.</string>
  <string name="err_cash_conflict">A cash session is running. Unable to switch to new cash register.</string>

  <string name="err_payleven_key">This application cannot connect to Payleven.</string>
  <string name="err_payleven_concurrent_call">An other transaction is running, please wait and retry.</string>
  <string name="err_payleven_general">Service unavailable, please try later.</string>
  <string name="err_payleven_forbidden">You cannot use Payleven in this country of for this currency.</string>

  <string name="err_json_read">Error while reading Json, data might be corrupted</string>

  <string name="err_save_local_customer">Error saving customer locally</string>
  <string name="err_save_online_customer">Error saving customer to server</string>
</resources>
